Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records circa 1860–1997 (bulk, 1880–1980) PR 53
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Rolled Drawings, 582 Linear feet in 142 boxes.
  - New Jersey
    - New Jersey—Far Hills | Lawson, Mr. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-045, Tube 152)
    - New Jersey—Gladstone | Turnbull, A[rthur]. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-014, Tube 044)
    - New Jersey—Gladstone | Turnbull, Arthur | Residence (Offsite-box RD-065, Tube 221)
    - New Jersey—Gladstone | Turnbull, Arthur | Residence (Offsite-box RD-091, Tube 299)
    - New Jersey—Gladstone | Turnbull, Arthur | Residence (Offsite-box RD-105, Tube 335)
    - New Jersey—Gladstone | Turnbull, Mr. | Farm cottage (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 284?)
    - New Jersey—Gladstone | Turnbull, Mr. | Farm cottage (Offsite-box RD-130, Tube 289?)
    - New Jersey—Gladstone | Turnbull, Mr. | Farm cottage (Offsite-box RD-133, Tube 289?)
    - New Jersey—Glen Gardner | New Jersey Sanatorium (Offsite-box RD-034, Tube 111)
    - New Jersey—Glen Gardner | New Jersey Sanatorium (Offsite-box RD-073, Tube 242)
    - New Jersey—Glen Gardner | New Jersey Sanatorium (Offsite-box RD-080, Tube 270)
    - New Jersey—Jersey City | Commercial Trust Company (Offsite-box RD-030, Tube 095)
    - New Jersey—Jersey City | Commercial Trust Company (Offsite-box RD-050, Tube 169)
    - New Jersey—Jersey City | Commercial Trust Company (Offsite-box RD-055, Tube 185)
    - New Jersey—Jersey City | Commercial Trust Company (Offsite-box RD-055, Tube 186)
    - New Jersey—Morristown | Bramhall, J. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-044, Tube 148)
    - New Jersey—Morristown | Buela, R. Residence (53 Miller Road) | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-033, Tube 109)
    - New Jersey—Morristown | Merrimac Realty Company (Sussex Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-065, Tube 218)
    - New Jersey—Morristown | Morris County Golf Club (Offsite-box RD-022, Tube 067-A)
    - New Jersey—Morristown | Morris County Golf Club (Offsite-box RD-022, Tube 067-B)
    - New Jersey—Morristown | South Hills | Plan of a housing development (Offsite-box RD-004, Tube 011)
    - New Jersey—Morristown | Spring Streams (Offsite-box RD-079, Tube 265)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Howard Savings Bank (Offsite-box RD-073, Tube 242)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Howard Savings Institute (Offsite-box RD-046, Tube 156)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Howard Savings Institute (Offsite-box RD-048, Tube 165)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Howard Savings Institute (Offsite-box RD-091, Tube 299)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Company (Offsite-box RD-017, Tube 052-A)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Company (Offsite-box RD-017, Tube 052-B)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Company (Offsite-box RD-054, Tube 184)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Company (Offsite-box RD-092, Tube 302-A)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Company (Offsite-box RD-093, Tube 302-B)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Company (Offsite-box RD-093, Tube 302-C)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Office Building (Broad & Clinton Streets) | Original drawings & alterations (Offsite-box RD-025, Tube 076)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Prudential Insurance Building (Offsite-box RD-092, Tube 301-A?)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Prudential Insurance Building (Offsite-box RD-092, Tube 301-B?)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Union National Building (Offsite-box RD-062, Tube 208)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Union Trust Co. (Offsite-box RD-066, Tube 223-A?)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Union Trust Co. (Offsite-box RD-066, Tube 223-B?)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Union Trust Co. (Offsite-box RD-067, Tube 223-C?)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Union Trust Co. (Offsite-box RD-067, Tube 223-D?)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Yardley Farm barn (Offsite-box RD-091, Tube 299)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Y.W.C.A. (now Rutgers Law School) (Offsite-box RD-002, Tube 006)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Y.W.C.A. | All scale drawings (Offsite-box RD-005, Tube 017-A)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Y.W.C.A. | All scale drawings (Offsite-box RD-005, Tube 017-B)
    - New Jersey—Newark | Y.W.C.A. (Offsite-box RD-058, Tube 198)
    - New Jersey—Paterson | United Bank Building (Offsite-box RD-029, Tube 090)
    - New Jersey—Paterson | United Bank Building (Offsite-box RD-067, Tube 225)
    - New Jersey—Peapack | Turnbull Residence (Offsite-box RD-018, Tube 055)
    - New Jersey—Somerville | First National Bank (Offsite-box RD-045, Tube 155)
    - New Jersey—Somerville | Somerville Public Library | Building (Offsite-box RD-021, Tube 062-A)
    - New Jersey—Somerville | Somerville Public Library | Building (Offsite-box RD-021, Tube 062-B)
    - New Jersey—Union | Union National Bank (Offsite-box RD-084, Tube 285)
    - New Jersey—Union | Union Trust Co. (Offsite-box RD-074, Tube 246)
  - New York
    - New York—Bayport (Long Island) | Post, R. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-006, Tube 019-A)
    - New York—Bayport (Long Island) | Post, R. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-006, Tube 019-B)
    - New York—Bayport (Long Island) | Post, R. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-006, Tube 019-C)
    - New York—Buffalo | Erie County Savings Bank (Offsite-box RD-019, Tube 058)
    - New York—Cedarhurst | Rockaway Hunting Club (Offsite-box RD-032, Tube 105)
    - New York—Elizabethtown | Windsor Hotel (annex) (Offsite-box RD-020, Tube 060)
    - New York—Elmira | Mark Twain Hotel (Offsite-box RD-036, Tube 118-B)
    - New York—Elmira | Mark Twain Hotel (Offsite-box RD-099, Tube 319-A)
    - New York—Elmira | Mark Twain Hotel (Offsite-box RD-100, Tube 319-B)
    - New York—Glens Falls | Glens Falls (Offsite-box RD-102, Tube 327-A)
    - New York—Glens Falls | Glens Falls (Offsite-box RD-103, Tube 327-B)
    - New York—Glens Falls | Glens Falls (Offsite-box RD-135, Tube 328)
    - New York—Glens Falls | Glens Falls Insurance Company (Offsite-box RD-113, Tube 361)
    - New York—Glens Falls | Glens Falls Insurance Company | Additions (Offsite-box RD-069, Tube 230)
    - New York—Glens Falls | Glens Falls Insurance Company | Additions (Offsite-box RD-071, Tube 237)
    - New York—Glens Falls | Glens Falls Insurance Company | Additions (Offsite-box RD-075, Tube 253)
    - New York—Glens Falls | Glens Falls Insurance Company | Additions (Offsite-box RD-078, Tube 260)
    - New York—Great Neck | Statler, E. M. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-026, Tube 080)
    - New York—Great Neck | Statler, E. M. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-048, Tube 164)
    - New York—Great Neck | Statler, E. M. | Residence additions & alterations (Offsite-box RD-034, Tube 112)
    - New York—Great Neck | Statler, E. M. | Residence alterations (Offsite-box RD-051, Tube 173-A)
    - New York—Great Neck | Statler's Restaurant | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-031, Tube 099)
    - New York—Long Island | Post, H.A.V. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-041, Tube 136)
    - New York—Long Island | Throop, E. T. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-010, Tube 031-032)
    - New York—Massena | Massena Hospital (Offsite-box RD-097, Tube 315-A)
    - New York—Massena | Massena Hospital (Offsite-box RD-098, Tube 315-B)
    - New York—Massena | Massena Hospital (Offsite-box RD-098, Tube 315-C)
    - New York—New Rochelle | Reinsurance Clearing House (Offsite-box RD-013, Tube 041)
    - New York—NYC—Bronx | Crotona Park | Public building (Offsite-box RD-049, Tube 166-A)
    - New York—NYC—Bronx | Crotona Park (Offsite-box RD-049, Tube 166-B/C)
    - New York—NYC—Bronx | Crotona Park (Offsite-box RD-068, Tube 226)
    - New York—NYC—Bronx | Lewis Morris Apartments | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-053, Tube 178)
    - New York—NYC—Bronx | Woodlawn Cemetery (between Walnut & Park Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 338)
    - New York—NYC—Bronx (Riverdale) | Kelley, W. F. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-036, Tube 117)
    - New York—NYC—Brooklyn | 39th Street Ferry House (Municipal Ferry) (Offsite-box RD-064, Tube 215)
    - New York—NYC—Brooklyn | Half Moon Hotel (Offsite-box RD-071, Tube 234)
    - New York—NYC—Brooklyn | Half Moon Hotel (Offsite-box RD-077, Tube 257)
    - New York—NYC—Brooklyn | Half Moon Hotel (Offsite-box RD-078, Tube 264-A)
    - New York—NYC—Brooklyn | Half Moon Hotel (Offsite-box RD-079, Tube 264-B)
    - New York—NYC—Brooklyn | Long Island Historical Society (Pierrepont Street) [later Brooklyn Historical Society, now Center for Brooklyn History] (Offsite-box RD-109, Tube 350-A)
    - New York—NYC—Brooklyn | Palmer, H. Y. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-021, Tube 063)
    - New York—NYC—Brooklyn | Palmer, R. U. | Residence (Offsite-box RD-050, Tube 171)
    - New York—NYC—Brooklyn | Permutit Building (54th Street & 1st Avenue) | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-023, Tube 068)
    - New York—NYC—Brooklyn | St. Martin's Roman Catholic Church | Blueprints (Offsite-box RD-046, Tube 159)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | 1 Park Row | Stores (Offsite-box RD-065, Tube 220)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | 6 East 69th Street | Residence—plans (Offsite-box RD-013, Tube 040-A?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | 9 East 40th Street (Offsite-box RD-067, Tube 225)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | 9 East 40th Street (Offsite-box RD-074, Tube 248)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | 9 East 57th Street (Offsite-box RD-034, Tube 112)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | 9 East 79th Street | Residence (Offsite-box RD-093, Tube 303-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | 9 East 79th Street | Residence (Offsite-box RD-093, Tube 303-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | 100 East 64th [68th?] Street | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-062, Tube 209)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | 235 East 72nd Street (Dr. Daw? Residence) | Proposed alterations (Offsite-box RD-091, Tube 299)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | American Surety Building (Pine Street) | Competition (Offsite-box RD-012, Tube 036-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | American Surety Building (Pine Street) | Competition (Offsite-box RD-012, Tube 036-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Apartment Building (2 East 63rd Street) (Offsite-box RD-072, Tube 240)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Bethlehem Chapel (196-198 Bleecker Street) (Offsite-box RD-040, Tube 135)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Broadway Building | Scale detail (Offsite-box RD-080, Tube 267)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Building (Broadway & Ann Street) [St. Paul Building?] (Offsite-box RD-039, Tube 128)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Building [Stores] (Broadway, Prince & Crosby Streets) (Offsite-box RD-072, Tube 238-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Building [Stores] (Broadway, Prince & Crosby Streets) (Offsite-box RD-072, Tube 238-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Child's Building (212-214 West 72nd Street) (Offsite-box RD-057, Tube 192)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Child's Building (214 West 72nd Street) | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-043, Tube 147)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Child's Building (724 Fifth Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-033, Tube 108)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Child's Building (724 Fifth Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-072, Tube 240)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Chemical Building (Offsite-box RD-072, Tube 238-A?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Chemical Building (Offsite-box RD-072, Tube 238-B?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Chemical Building (Baskerville) (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 261)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Chemical Building (Furniture & Equipment) (Offsite-box RD-118, Tube 373-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Chemical Building (Furniture & Equipment) (Offsite-box RD-118, Tube 373-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Chemical Building (Furniture & Equipment) (Offsite-box RD-119, Tube 373-C)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Gym & Vocational Building (Offsite-box RD-068, Tube 227-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Gymnasium & Vocational Building (Wingate) (Offsite-box RD-075, Tube 250)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Gymnasium (Offsite-box RD-070, Tube 232)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Gymnasium (Offsite-box RD-076, Tube 255-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Offsite-box RD-115, Tube 368-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Offsite-box RD-115, Tube 368-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building 1/4 scale (Offsite-box RD-116, Tube 369-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building 1/4 scale (Offsite-box RD-116, Tube 369-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Furniture) (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 376)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Electric Work) (Offsite-box RD-119, Tube 377)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (General Plans) (Offsite-box RD-120, Tube 378)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Details) (Offsite-box RD-120, Tube 379-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Details) (Offsite-box RD-120, Tube 379-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Details) (Offsite-box RD-120, Tube 380-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Details) (Offsite-box RD-121, Tube 380-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Offsite-box RD-121, Tube 381)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Offsite-box RD-121, Tube 382-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Offsite-box RD-121, Tube 382-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Offsite-box RD-122, Tube 382-C)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Offsite-box RD-122, Tube 382-D)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 383)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Offsite-box RD-122, Tube 384-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Offsite-box RD-122, Tube 384-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Offsite-box RD-123, Tube 384-C)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Main Building (Offsite-box RD-123, Tube 384-D)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building (Offsite-box RD-068, Tube 226)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building (Offsite-box RD-070, Tube 233-A?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building (Offsite-box RD-070, Tube 233-B?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 249)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building (Offsite-box RD-076, Tube 256-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building (Offsite-box RD-076, Tube 256-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building (Offsite-box RD-077, Tube 256-C)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 375)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building (Steel shop drawings) (Offsite-box RD-117, Tube 371)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building (Chemical Building) (Offsite-box RD-117, Tube 372-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building (Chemical Building) (Offsite-box RD-118, Tube 372-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Mechanical Arts Building (Chemical Building) (Offsite-box RD-118, Tube 372-C)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Sub-Freshman Building (Offsite-box RD-068, Tube 228-A?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Sub-Freshman Building (Offsite-box RD-069, Tube 228-B?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Sub-Freshman Building (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 251)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Sub-Freshman Building (Offsite-box RD-116, Tube 370-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Sub-Freshman Building (Offsite-box RD-116, Tube 370-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Sub-Freshman Building (Offsite-box RD-117, Tube 370-C)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Sub-Freshman Building (Offsite-box RD-117, Tube 370-D)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Sub-Freshman Building (Offsite-box RD-119, Tube 374-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | City College of New York | Sub-Freshman Building (Offsite-box RD-119, Tube 374-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Coe, Henry E. | 636-638 Broadway | Plans (Offsite-box RD-023, Tube 070)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Crisp Apartment House (602-608 East 84th Street) (Offsite-box RD-069, Tube 231-A?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Crisp Apartment House (602-608 East 84th Street) (Offsite-box RD-070, Tube 231-B?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Crisp Apartment House (602-608 East 84th Street) (Offsite-box RD-075, Tube 254-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Crisp Apartment House (602-608 East 84th Street) (Offsite-box RD-076, Tube 254-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | East River Apartment Project (Offsite-box RD-007, Tube 021-022)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | East River Apartment Project (Offsite-box RD-064, Tube 214)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | East River Apartment Project (Offsite-box RD-066, Tube 222-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | East River Drive Apartment Houses (Offsite-box RD-091, Tube 299)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | East River Garden Apartment Project (Offsite-box RD-014, Tube 042)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | East River Garden Apartment Project (Offsite-box RD-036, Tube 118-C)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | East River Garden Apartment Project (Offsite-box RD-067, Tube 223-D)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | East River Garden Apartment Project (Offsite-box RD-073, Tube 241)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Governor Clinton Hotel (31st Street & 7th Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-047, Tube 161)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | [Governor?] Clinton Hotel | Drawings (Offsite-box RD-066, Tube 223-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | [Governor?] Clinton Hotel | Drawings (Offsite-box RD-066, Tube 223-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | [Governor?] Clinton Hotel | Drawings (Offsite-box RD-067, Tube 223-C)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Great Nothern Hotel | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-033, Tube 106)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Halsey, Charles D. | Residence (49 East 72nd Street) (Offsite-box RD-022, Tube 065)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Havemeyer Building (Dey & Church Streets) (Offsite-box RD-031, Tube 097)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Havemeyer Building (Dey & Church Streets) 97 (Offsite-box RD-038, Tube 125)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Havemeyer Building (Dey & Church Streets) (Offsite-box RD-042, Tube 142-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Havemeyer Building (Dey & Church Streets) (Offsite-box RD-042, Tube 142-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Havemeyer Building (Dey & Church Streets) (Offsite-box RD-102, Tube 325)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Hearst Magazine Building (Eighth Avenue between 56th & 57th Streets) | Additions & alterations (Offsite-box RD-110, Tube 351)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Hearst Magazine Building (Eighth Avenue between 56th & 57th Streets) (Offsite-box RD-110, Tube 352)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Hearst Magazine Building (Eighth Avenue between 56th & 57th Streets) (Offsite-box RD-110, Tube 353-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Hearst Magazine Building (Eighth Avenue between 56th & 57th Streets) (Offsite-box RD-111, Tube 353-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Hearst Magazine Building (Eighth Avenue between 56th & 57th Streets) (Offsite-box RD-111, Tube 354-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Hearst Magazine Building (Eighth Avenue between 56th & 57th Streets) (Offsite-box RD-111, Tube 354-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Hearst Magazine Building (Eighth Avenue between 56th & 57th Streets) (Offsite-box RD-111, Tube 355)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Hearst Magazine Building (Eighth Avenue between 56th & 57th Streets) | Additions & alterations (Offsite-box RD-112, Tube 356-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Hearst Magazine Building (Eighth Avenue between 56th & 57th Streets) | Additions & alterations (Offsite-box RD-112, Tube 356-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Manhattan Life Insurance Co. | Competition drawing (Offsite-box RD-092, Tube 301-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Martha Washington Hotel (Offsite-box RD-061, Tube 205)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Matchette Investment Company | Matchette Apartments and penthouse (817 Fifth Avenue) (Offsite-box RD-073, Tube 243)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Matchette Investment Company | Matchette Apartments (2 East 63rd Street) | Survey (Offsite-box RD-027, Tube 087-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Matchette Investment Company | Matchette Apartments (2 East 63rd Street) | Survey (Offsite-box RD-051, Tube 174-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Matchette Investment Company | Matchette Apartments (2 East 63rd Street | Survey (Offsite-box RD-072, Tube 240)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Matchette Investment Company | Matchette Apartments (2 East 63rd Street | Survey (Offsite-box RD-078, Tube 263)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Meyer Jonasson | Stores (817 Broadway & 12th Street) | Terra Cotta (Offsite-box RD-016, Tube 050-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Meyer Jonasson | Stores (817 Broadway & 12th Street) | Terra Cotta (Offsite-box RD-017, Tube 050-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Meyer Jonasson | Stores (817 Broadway & 12th Street) | Alterations (trace) (Offsite-box RD-019, Tube 059-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Meyer Jonasson | Stores (817 Broadway & 12th Street) | Alterations (trace) (Offsite-box RD-020, Tube 059-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | National Arts Club | Studio Building (15 Gramercy Park South) (Offsite-box RD-042, Tube 143-A?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | National Arts Club | Studio Building (15 Gramercy Park South) (Offsite-box RD-043, Tube 143-B?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | Netherlands Hotel (5th Avenue & 59th Street) | Power plant alterations (Offsite-box RD-035, Tube 114)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York City Omnibus Company | Proposed garage & gasoline storage systems (Offsite-box RD-014, Tube 044)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Clearing House (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 039)
      Location
      This item is stored onsite in 2NW/Unit 1B/Bay 2/Drawer 15.
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Cotton Exchange | 1 drawing of fireplace in smoking room (Offsite-box RD-083, Tube 280-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Life Insurance Co. | Competition drawing (Offsite-box RD-092, Tube 301-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Blueprints (Offsite-box RD-081, Tube 273-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Blueprints (Offsite-box RD-081, Tube 273-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Blueprints (Offsite-box RD-082, Tube 278-A)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Blueprints (Offsite-box RD-082, Tube 278-B)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Carpenter work (Offsite-box RD-015, Tube 046-A?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Carpenter work (Offsite-box RD-015, Tube 046-B?)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Detail plans (Offsite-box RD-071, Tube 234)
    - New York—NYC—Manhattan | New York Produce Exchange | Foundation plans (Offsite-box RD-014, Tube 042)